我們人民[美國憲法序言]
美屬薩摩亞大學
索爾·古德曼
法學博士
喂
Yeah.
你知不知道現在幾點了
Do you have any idea what time it is?
心急吃不了熱豆腐  弗朗西斯卡
Watched pot never boils, Francesca.
已經一小時了
It's been an hour.
外面大堂一堆人呢
You've got a lobby full of people out here,
我八點準時下班
and at eight o'clock, I am done.
哪怕你這里燒毀了我都不管
I don't care if the building burns down,
我要回家了
I'm going home.
看看你  還有你的職業道德
Wow, you and your work ethic.
我沒告訴過你  缺你不可嗎
Did I ever tell you how indispensable you are?
沒有嗎
No?
還要多久  索爾
How much longer, Saul?
怎么說呢  我也說不好
You know what? I can't say.
向大家致以我最誠摯的歉意
So pass along my sincerest apologies
告訴他們我實在忙不過來
and tell 'em I'm swamped.
誰都能聽見你在扔那破玩意
Everyone can hear you bouncing that thing.
那是思考的聲音
That's the sound of thinking.
你有空也應該試試
You should try it sometime.
人人影視
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
字幕組招新中
請訪問 yysub.net
翻譯    Margaery  Eunice  肉松
翻譯    杏仁斯嘉麗  吃冰棒
離婚申訴書(無子女)
離婚訴訟原告  金柏莉·韋克斯勒
翻譯    子V   joy_bwl
校對    杏仁斯嘉麗   Eunice
時間軸    今   大蔥
喂
Yeah?
還等什么
What are you waiting for?
讓她進來
Send her in.
后期    8T
總監    喃喃
絕命律師
第六季第十二集
怎么樣
How's it coming?
挺好
Good.
你買蛋黃醬了嗎
Did you get the mayonnaise?
是這樣的
Well, here's the thing,
他們沒有杜克牌的了  我非常喜歡杜克牌
they didn't have Duke's, and I really like Duke's.
可是他們沒有  有點掃興
But they didn't have it, which is a bummer. So...
我也不懂
I dunno.
你覺得這個行嗎
Think this'll work?
嚴格說來  這不是真正的蛋黃醬  但...
I mean, technically, it isn't actually mayonnaise, but...
嗯
Yeah,
嚴格說來  我認為這不是蛋黃醬
technically, I don't think this is mayonnaise.
但是類似吧
But close, right?
你覺得呢  要不要試試
What do you think? Should we give it a shot?
我也不知道  你覺得呢
I dunno. What do you think?
嗯
Yeah.
咱們試試
Let's give it a shot.
天啊
Oh, my gosh.
我也說不好  我盡力了
I don't know. It's as close as I could get.
西西  石榴紅配金色  太明顯了
Cissy, garnet and gold! I see it plain as day.
而且  這也太漂亮了  西西
Plus, they're really beautiful, Cissy.
紅色的還能冒充一下石榴紅
Ah, the red ones could maybe pass for garnet.
但是金色的就是普通的黃色
But the "Gold" ones are just regular yellow.
我一看見就脫口而出"佛羅里達州立大學隊"
Well, the minute I saw them I said, "FSU!"
況且  金色食用色素
Besides, gold food coloring?
瓊  你聽說過嗎
June, did you ever even hear of that?
沒有  聽著就貴
No! Sounds expensive.
就算真有這種東西
And if they even make such a thing,
那里邊的添加劑
you'd probably get flipper-hands
很可能會害你手上長蹼
from all the chemicals they'd put in it.
好吧
Well...
反正我是盡最大努力了
This is as close as I could get, anyway.
-太完美了  西西  -謝謝
- Oh, it's perfect, Cissy. - Thank you.
-天啊  -這太漂亮了
- Oh, my gosh. - Ah, this is all so beautiful.
-所有的看著都美極了  -非常有食欲
- Everything looks amazing. - Looks delicious.
-勺子忘了  不好意思  -我講講環氧樹脂
- Oh, I forgot spoons. Sorry. - Well, let me tell you about epoxy--
環氧樹脂會發黃
Epoxy yellows.
它暴露在陽光下...
You hit it with enough sunlight...
-不  -他說得對
- No. Well-- - He's right.
-不是吧  -是的  他說得沒錯
- Wait, no. - No, he's right.
如果你用顏色足夠深的地板
If you just use a dark enough floor--
哥幾個  聽我說  這事爭論不完
Guys, I'm telling you, we're never gonna settle this.
這事我天天吵
I've been having this argument five days a week,
但現在我都變成瑞典了
but now I'm Sweden.
-是瑞士[中立不選邊]  -喝點什么
- Switzerland. - You want something to drink?
-酒柜  -太好了  西西
- Wine coolers? - Great. Cissy?
馬文不喜歡我喝酒
Marvin doesn't like me to drink.
西西  我們早晚要送你一個酒柜
Cissy, we're gonna get a wine cooler down you one day.
挺有趣的
That was fun.
沒錯  是很有趣
Yeah. That was fun.
對了  就是那
That's it right there.
干得好  朋友們
Good job, guys.
"彼得大帝就埋藏于我身體里"
"Peter the Great is buried inside me."
-"來找我..."  -她說什么
- "Find me in..." - What did she say?
我們得互相幫助
We're gonna help each other.
我說  上這個節目沒點身材怎么行
Boy, you gotta be in shape to be on this show.
可不是嘛
You sure do.
跑量很大
Lotsa running.
是的
Yeah.
他們在這個節目上跟牛賽跑過嗎
You think they ever ran with the bulls on this show?
西班牙那種
Like, in Spain?
應該是沒見過
Not that we've seen, I don't think.
也許太危險了
Maybe it's too dangerous.
你覺得呢
What do you think?
可能吧
Maybe.
我覺得那盤土豆沙拉大受歡迎
Oh, I thought the potato salad worked out great.
-真的嗎  -是啊
- You think? - Yep.
好像又下雨了
Looks like rain again.
是的
Yeah. Does.
衛星沙灘新開了一家澳拜客
Oh, hey, they opened a new Outback down in Satellite Beach.
-周五去嗎  -行
- You wanna go Friday? - Sure.
是約會哦
It's a date.
棕櫚海岸灑水器
我不想拒絕給她買玩具  但我又...
I don't want to not buy her toys, but I also...
金·韋克斯勒  產品目錄宣傳冊
棕櫚海岸灑水器
麻煩告訴我212-17\H型號的法蘭盤直徑
Could you tell me the flange diameter of 212-dash-17-backslash-H?
行
Great.
冒口是三英寸還是兩英寸
And does that come in a three-inch riser, or just the two-inch?
行
Great.
材料是ABS還是PVC
ABS or PVC?
行
Oh. Great.
我們五點開始唱歌
We're gonna sing at 5:00.
好
Oh. Great.
我看看
Let me see.
生快
你喵了個完美  我可沒開喵了個玩笑
真可愛  瓊
That's cute, June.
我午飯后去取蛋糕
I'll pick up the cake after lunch.
你知道譚美喜歡什么冰淇淋嗎
Do you remember what kind of ice cream Tammy likes?
-天啊  不清楚  -那你覺得呢
- Uh... geez, no. - Yeah. So maybe... What do you think?
香草
Vanilla?
還是草莓
Or strawberry?
都不錯
They're both good.
是吧
I know, right?
-五點哦  -行
- Five o'clock. - Okay, great.
沒人造那么長的
No, nobody makes it that long.
你...你想想看
Well, I mean, because-- I mean, think about it.
《排水溝系統》
總得裝得進卡車吧
It's got to fit in the truck, right?
那怎么裝得進卡車呢
So, how's it gonna fit in the truck if--
但沒人能把卡車造那么長  所以
Well, yeah, but nobody makes a truck that long, so...
可以肯定地說
Safe to say.
好吧  抱歉無法提供服務
Okay. Well, sorry we couldn't be of service.
那可卡因呢
So... whatever happened to crack?
怎么現在新聞上見不到了呢
How come you never hear about it on the news anymore?
大家都不吸了那東西了嗎
Did everybody just all decide to stop taking it?
那個讓你跳舞還要吸奶嘴的毒品
What's the drug that makes you dance around
叫什么來著
and put a pacifier in your mouth?
-搖頭丸  -搖頭丸
- Ecstasy. - Ecstasy!
現在這個可流行了  我想他們
That's the big one now. I think that they have--
沒錯  可流行了
Yeah. That's the big one.
我姐妹閨蜜的兒子
My sister's best friend's son?
天啊
Oh, my God...
但我不懂奶嘴的事
But I don't understand the pacifier.
為什么他們都需要奶嘴
Why would they all need pacifiers?
如果你是商店老板
Like, don't you think if you ran a store
青少年闖進店里
and some teenager came in your store
想買奶嘴
and tried to buy a pacifier,
難道你不報警嗎
don't you think you'd call the police?
-是啊  -要我肯定會
- Yeah. - Pbht! I sure would.
-絕對的  -你在吃什么
- Absolutely. - Whatcha eating?
金槍魚沙拉
Tuna salad.
我用奇妙沙拉醬做的  而不是蛋黃醬
I made it with Miracle Whip instead of mayonnaise.
我用杏仁醬而不是花生醬
I use almond butter instead of pean--
棕櫚海岸灑水器
開啟了新篇章...
我今早醒來時
When I woke up this morning,
猜我客廳里有什么
guess what was in my living room.
居然有一輛健身單車
A freaking exercise bike.
難以置信那是他給我的生日禮物
Yeah. I can't believe he got that for my birthday.
等等
Hold on a second.
棕櫚海岸灑水器  從1978年開始澆灌你的世界
Palm Coast Sprinkler, watering your world since 1978.
稍等
Please hold.
什么事
Yep?
金  維克多·圣克萊爾找你  三號線
Kim, there's a Viktor St. Claire for you on line three.
金
Kim?
好的
Uh, yep. Okay.
你怎么看
Yeah. So, what do you think about that?
真的很不禮貌
That's pretty rude.
什么牌子
What brand is it?
我才不管誰造的呢
I don't care who made it.
我才不管是威震天三千還是值四百萬呢
I don't care if it's Megatron 3000 or worth $4 million.
我要直接騎著送回店里去
I'm gonna ride it straight back to the store,
你猜他會收到什么生日禮物
and guess what he's gonna get for his next birthday.
生發精華吧
Some hair regrowth serum,
我還要取笑他
and I'm gonna laugh at him.
沒錯
Yeah.
我是金·韋克斯勒
Kim Wexler.
你好  金
Hey, Kim.
你知道我是誰嗎
You know who this is?
我就當你知道了
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
你們那位前臺
Uh, that receptionist of yours,
她是喜歡偷聽的人嗎
is she the type to listen in?
-不是  -那就好
- No. - Good.
好的
Okay.
你在佛羅里達過得還好嗎
So, how's Florida been treating you?
希望這會兒沒有颶風
I'm catching you between hurricanes, I hope.
金  你在聽嗎
Kim, you there?
你有什么事
What do you want?
我...沒什么事
I don't-- I don't want anything.
就是
I just...
很久沒聯絡了
It's been a while, you know?
我想著我們很久沒聯絡了
Just-- I'm thinking it's been a while,
敘敘舊也挺好的
and, um, might be nice to catch up.
-"敘舊"  -是的
- "Catch up." - Yeah.
今早我思緒神游
My mind was wandering this morning. I was just...
沒想什么特別的事  就是胡思亂想
Not thinking anything in particular. Just random thoughts.
我突然發覺已經過去六年了
And, bam, it suddenly occurred to me it's been six years.
天啊
I mean, Jesus.
真不敢相信
I, I couldn't believe it.
你可能想知道我還活著
I thought you might wanna know I'm still alive.
對
Yep.
我好好的  仍然逍遙法外
I'm still out here, still getting away with it.
聯調局那些笨蛋連自己的屁股都找不到
The feds couldn't find their own ass
更別說抓我了
with both hands and a proctologist.
你不該打給我
You shouldn't be calling me.
你醒了
Oh, hey! You're awake!
你不該打來
You shouldn't be calling.
為什么  我占線
Why not? What, am I tying up the line
影響重要的灌溉業務了嗎
for important irrigation business?
拜托  金  說句話吧
I mean, come on, Kim. Say something.
你可以罵我混蛋  沖我發火
You can call me an asshole, yell at me.
讓我知道你依然有一口氣
Just let me know you've still got a pulse.
說句話啊
Just say something.
你想要我開口
You want me to say something?
是的
Yeah.
你應該去自首
You should turn yourself in.
什么
Do what?
你聽見了
You heard me.
我不知道你一直過著什么樣的生活
I don't know what kind of life you've been living,
但肯定沒多風光
but it can't be much.
真是五十步笑百步
Said the pot to the kettle!
簡直...
What-- That is--
荒謬至極  你竟然對我說教
That is really rich, you-- You preaching to me?
你并不知道我做過或沒做過什么
See, you have no idea what I did or didn't do, okay?
再說了  你怎么不去自首
A-And why don't you turn yourself in,
既然你那么有罪惡感
seeing as how you're the one with the guilty conscience, huh?
是什么阻止了你
What-- What is stopping you?
弗林死了
Fring's in the ground.
麥克死了  拉羅也死了
Mike's in the ground. Lalo's in the ground.
聽說是這樣
Apparently.
你不必為了我而猶豫不決
You don't have to hold back on my account.
他們只能處死我一次  所以你盡管去吧
They can only hang me once. So-- So go ahead.
全說出來  自我懲罰吧  看對你有什么好處
Spill your guts! Put on your hair shirt, see what it gets you!
為...
Why--
金  我們為什么說起自首
Kim, why are we even talking about this?
我們都很聰明  不會無緣無故毀掉自己人生
We're both too smart to throw our lives away for no reason.
我...
Just...
我只是想...
I just... I only wanted to...
金
Kim.
Kim?
金
Kim.
我很高興你還活著
I'm glad you're alive.
什么事
Yeah?
該唱歌了
Time to sing!
好的
Okay.
*祝你生日快樂*
*Happy birthday to you*
*祝你生日快樂  親愛的譚美*
*Happy birthday, dear Tammy*
*祝你生日快樂*
*Happy birthday to you*
阿拉斯加
阿爾布開克
法官讓你走之前我不能離開
I can't leave before the judge dismisses you.
我保證讓他們知道
I'll make sure they're aware.
就記住坐直身子
Now, just remember to sit up straight
法官跟你說話時認真聽
and listen carefully when the judge addresses you.
保持專心  注意力集中
Stay attentive and engaged.
就算你不確定發生什么事了  也別表現出來
Even if you're not so sure what's going on, don't show it.
好了  過來
All right. Come here.
-把襯衫下擺掖進褲子里去  -好的
- Tuck your shirt in for me, will you? - Okay.
你要給法官一個好印象
You gotta look good for the judge.
因為你有前科
Because of your record...
金
Kim?
你好  謝麗爾
Hi, Cheryl.
我在門口
I'm out front.
塞拉曼加離開后不久  吉米和我就開始謀劃一次長期行動  讓人懷疑霍華德·哈姆林的品格
為了私利...
破壞霍華德...
假造他可卡因成癮
塞拉曼加進入了我們家...  頭部中槍  霍華德立即死亡
我按照指示  開車去弗林家
厄門紹特毀滅證據...
...偽裝成自殺...
霍華德是被人殺害的
Howard was murdered?
為什么
Why?
他...
He was...
不該在那時出現在那里
in the wrong place at the wrong time.
他的尸體在哪
Where's his body?
我不知道
I don't know.
警方呢
And the police?
會再搜尋嗎
Will they search again?
會的
They'll search.
我覺得他們應該找不到
I don't think they'll find him.
謝麗爾  他...
Cheryl, he...
都發生在一瞬間
It-- it all happened in an instant.
他沒有受苦
And he didn't-- he didn't suffer.
"他沒有受苦"
"He didn't suffer."
你倆編出的謊言
The lies you two made up.
你們描繪出的那個他
The picture you painted.
他現在完全是那個人了
That's all he is now.
所有人只記得那樣的他
That's all anybody remembers.
我想改變現狀
I want to change that.
接下來會怎么樣
What happens now?
你會受審嗎
Will you be tried?
你會坐牢嗎
Will you go to jail?
我不知道
I don't know.
你是律師  對嗎
You're a lawyer, right?
你是個了不起的律師  霍華德說的
You're a-- A great one, Howard said!
你怎么能不知道
How could you not know?
我把宣誓口供交給了伯納利歐縣
Bernalillo County has my affidavit.
是否起訴要看地檢官
It's up to the district attorney whether to prosecute.
她可能不會起訴
And she may not.
為什么
Why?
沒有確鑿證據
There's no physical evidence.
除了我的前夫以外沒有證人
No remaining witnesses other than my ex-husband,
如果我的前夫還活著的話
assuming he's still alive.
我可以在民事法庭起訴你
I could sue you in civil court.
我可以拿走你的一切
I could take everything you've got.
對
Yeah.
你為什么這么做
Why are you doing this?
天啊
Oh, God!
投資報告
密碼  密碼
Passwords. Passwords...
一個帽子收藏家
A hat man.
自由奔跑吧  銹銹
該死
Holy shit.
這里沒什么好看的
Nothing to see here.
走吧
Move on.
看看這破玩意
Look at this bullshit.
看啊
Look.
看  你管這叫什么
Look. What would you call this?
我...
I'd call that...
我不知道  什么
I dunno, what?
這叫魚肉玉米卷餅嗎
Would you call that a fish taco?
誰管這叫魚肉玉米卷餅啊  合法嗎
Could anybody call this a fish taco? I mean, legally?
別在我面前晃悠它了
Stop waving that thing at me.
看看它
Look at this!
只有一片鱈魚
There's one piece of goddamned pollock
還沒我大拇指尖大呢
no bigger than the end of my thumb.
怎么能管它叫...
Now, how can you even call that a--
你跟我說有用嗎
Like am I s'posed to do something?
你想讓我怎么辦
What do you want me to do about it?
我想讓你看看  告訴我你看到了什么
Well, I want you to look inside there and tell me what you see.
你會不會把這玩意賣給毫無防備的百姓
W-Would you or would you not sell this to an unsuspecting public?
你為什么堅持點魚肉
Why do you persist in ordering fish
我們離最近的海有2200多公里
when we're 1,400 miles away from the nearest ocean?
因為菜單上有魚肉  明白嗎
Because it's on the menu, all right?
因為我活在21世紀  明白嗎
Because I live in the 21st goddamn century, all right?
這玩意就是屎
And this? This is some bullshit.
我跟你說  我恨不得回去
I'm telling you, I got half a mind to go on back over there
扇人一耳光
and smack somebody in their face there.
離婚訴訟原告簽名
金柏莉·韋克斯勒
好
Yes!
你覺得怎么樣
What do you think?
挺不錯的吧
Pretty great, right?
對  都很...
Yeah, it's, um...
嗯
Yep.
需要你的印刷體姓名和簽名
I just need your printed name and signature.
佛羅里達
So, Florida.
佛羅里達  佛羅里達  佛羅里達
Florida, Florida, Florida...
為什么選那
Why there?
-我想是...  -無所謂
- I guess-- - It doesn't matter.
不一定要有原因
Doesn't have to make sense.
我得告訴你  我覺得你會后悔的
Hey, I gotta tell you, I think you're gonna regret
沒收下你磯鷂渡的那份錢
not taking your share of the Sandpiper money.
那筆錢夠買一大片沼澤地了
That'd buy a shitload of swampland.
我...
I will, um,
明天會去提交申請
file these tomorrow.
好的
All right. Well.
祝你生活美滿  金
Have a nice life, Kim.
美女  下一位是誰
Hey, Sweetcheeks, who do we got next?
開始掙錢了
Let's make some money!
埃米利奧·小山
Emilio Koyama!
你的訴訟文件呢
Where's your paperwork?
我從來不碰文件
I don't do no paperwork.
他不碰文件
He doesn't do paperwork!
誰在乎呢  來吧  來吧
Who cares? Come on, come on.
可以借根煙抽嗎
Hey, yo, could I bum one of those?
謝謝
Thanks.
這是什么鬼天氣
What's up with this shit?
下雨了
Rainy.
知道  不過這雨也太夸張了
Yeah. No. It-- It's crazy.
真令人抓狂
It's like bananas, all this rain.
我們不是在沙漠地區嗎
I mean, I thought we were, like, in a desert, you know?
你是律師  對嗎
You're a lawyer, right?
我認得你
I recognize you.
你為我兄弟康寶辯護過
You defended my buddy Combo.
克里斯蒂安·奧特加
Christian Ortega.
少年法庭  偷了個嬰兒耶穌
Juvie court, stole a Baby Jesus.
不是真的嬰兒  只是個...
I mean, not like a real baby, just a--
就是放在教堂外面的東西
You know, one of those things outside of the church.
-耶誕布景  -對
- Nativity scene. - Yeah.
哥倫布騎士團
Knights of Columbus.
我就納了悶了  他要那玩意干什么
I mean, what the hell did he even want that thing for?
我到現在都沒想明白
I mean, I-- I still don't know.
傻逼
Dumbass.
我告訴過他  偷那種東西
I told him he could go to Hell
會下地獄的
for stealing something like that, I mean.
可他聽我的了嗎  沒有
But did he listen to me? No.
但是你  你幫他脫了罪  不用受罰  那真是...
But you, you got him off, like, scot-free. That--
那真是太屌了
That was pretty slick, yo.
告訴他  我希望他不要惹麻煩
Well, tell him I hope he's keeping his nose clean.
對  對  你說得對
Yeah, yeah, right on.
必須的
Absolutely.
你瞧你這么專業
Hey, so, you having all this expertise and all...
這個古德曼
This guy Goodman?
他有真本事嗎
He the real deal?
是正經律師嗎
Like, lawyer-wise?
為什么這么問
Why do you ask?
我里面有個兄弟  犯了很嚴重的事
I got a buddy in there who's facing some serious time.
不是偷嬰兒耶穌那種小事
I mean, not-- you know, not Baby Jesus-time,
是很嚴重的
but... but serious.
他需要一流的代理律師
You know, he needs top-shelf legal representation.
我是這么告訴他的
And I tell him that, right?
但是他看到了這家伙的電視廣告
But, you know, he sees this dude's commercials on TV
就想來找他
and this is where he wants to go.
我跟他說  "埃米利奧  搞笑電視廣告
And I tell him, "Yo, Emilio, you know, a funny TV commercial
并不是可靠的根據"
is not a sound basis for, like, you know..."
你會僅憑一支搞笑電視廣告
I mean, like, would you go to doctor to do, like,
就去找那個醫生
an operation on you in like a--
給你的脾之類的
on, like, your spleen or whatever
動手術嗎
on the fact of a funny TV commercial?
不會  別鬧了
No. I mean, come on.
這有什么區別
How is this any different?
你說呢
You know?
話說回來
Anyway...
這人靠譜嗎
Is this guy any good?
我認識他的時候  他是靠譜的
When I knew him, he was.
喂
Hello?
你好  爸
Hey, uh, Dad?
是我  我是杰夫
It's me. It's-- It's Jeff.
杰夫  現在幾點了
Jeff? What time is it?
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
我不太好
Yeah, no, not really.
那個  我...
Um, I, uh...
爸  我被捕了
Dad, I got arrested.
不
Oh, no.
為什么  小杰
What for? Jeffie.
這是個天大的誤會
It's like this crazy mistake, you know?
我出了車禍
I mean, I had an accident, okay?
就是點小擦撞  不嚴重
A, a little fender-bender type deal, no, no big thing.
我的腳可能不小心踩到了油門上
My foot maybe slipped on the accelerator,
也可能是車子出了什么故障  我不知道
or maybe it was a defective-- I dunno.
但這不是重點
But that's not the big-deal part.
重點是
The big-deal part is,
他們認為我  我本人  犯了搶劫罪
they think that I, me, committed a robbery.
他們怎么會這么想
And why would they think that?
就是說啊
I know, right?
我出車禍的那個地方
The place where I had the accident?
有個男的  是醉漢
This guy? This drunk guy?
他從自己家里晃晃悠悠地走出來
He comes wandering out of his house
攔住了死條子  是警察  說什么
and flags down the cops, the, the police, and says,
"我被打劫了"
"Hey, you know, I got robbed!"
當然了  警察呢
And sure enough, the police?
找到了破門闖入的證據
They find evidence of, like, breaking and entering.
家里也有東西不見了  但這都不是我干的
And, and, and stuff is missing, which I did not do.
沒錯  就這樣
And, uh... yeah. Like that.
這么說警察肯定是找錯人了
Well, the police are obviously barking up the wrong tree.
可不是嗎  找錯人了
Yeah. No shit, wrong tree!
-大錯特錯  -就是
- Wrong, like, forest. - Exactly.
因為你絕不會做出這種事
Because you would never do something like that,
對不對  兒子
would you, son?
當然不會  絕對不會
No. No. No way, man. Absolutely not.
那警察逮捕你的時候
Uh, when the police took you into custody,
他們有發現任何所謂的被盜物品嗎
did they find any of this so-called stolen merchandise?
有在你身上發現嗎
Was it in your possession?
-沒有  -當然沒有
- No. - Of course it wasn't.
因為你根本就沒有偷東西
Because you didn't steal anything.
因此  既然沒有
Therefore, since there's no evidence whatsoever
你犯下了任何罪的相關證據
that you committed any crime,
你就沒什么好擔心的了
I'd say you got nothing to worry about.
那之后怎么辦
So, what happens next?
深呼吸  安心坐等
Breathe deep and sit tight.
我午飯前就接你出去
I'll have you out by lunchtime.
你自己過來嗎
You coming down here yourself?
還是叫你媽去吧
Nah, I think it'll be your mom.
你會替我通知她嗎
You'll talk to her for me?
當然了
I sure will.
我全都會搞定  沒問題的
I'll straighten it all out, no problem.
那好的
Yeah, okay. Good.
杰夫  你會得到
Jeff, you're gonna get
全世界最厲害的法律辯護
the best legal defense in the whole wide world.
就相信你老爹吧
Trust your old man on that.
好的  收到  安心坐等
Okay, copy that. Sit tight.
沒錯
You do that.
別著急
Keep your shirt on.
喂
Hello?
吉恩
Gene.
吉恩  親愛的  你知道這才幾點嗎
Gene, Honey, do you know what time it is?
天吶  那個不孝子
Oh. Oh, God. That boy.
我早晚會被他氣死的
He's gonna put me in my grave.
瑪麗恩
Marion.
就是鬧了個誤會
It's a mistake, is all.
因為自己沒做過的事而進局子
Getting picked up for something you didn't do?
誰都可能會碰到
That could happen to anybody.
才怪
Yeah, right, anyone.
這不是他第一次了
This isn't the first time, you know.
他之前也惹過麻煩
He's been in trouble before.
老天啊
Oh, Jesus.
-瑪麗恩  -這個克星
- Marion... - The death of me.
我會被他活活氣死
He's gonna be the death of me.
瑪麗恩  瑪麗恩  沒事的
Marion. Marion, it's gonna be all right.
我們立馬就能接他出來
We'll get him outta there lickety-split.
我經歷過這種情況
I've been through this before.
可費時間了
There's nothing lickety-split about it.
他還住在阿爾布開克的時候
Back when he was living in Albuquerque?
公共場所醉酒  拒捕
Drunk in public, resisting arrest,
在不應該的地方小便
urinating in someplace he shouldn't have.
而我打了好幾個小時的長途電話
And me on the telephone for hours, long distance,
就為了給他找保釋公司
trying to find him one of those bail-out places.
我信用卡都刷爆了
I maxed out my Discover card.
到現在都在還款
I'm still paying for that one.
錢不成問題
Well, money's not gonna be a problem,
因為我會幫你
'cause I'm gonna help you with that.
不行  吉恩  我怎么好意思
No. Gene, I can't let you do that. No.
當然好意思  杰夫以后可以還我
Sure you can. Jeff'll pay me back.
你也不用擔心擔保人的事
And you don't have to worry about a bondsman, either.
因為知道嗎
Because guess what?
奧馬哈根本就沒這一套
In Omaha, they don't have 'em.
你直接去警察局
All right? You just walk into the station
用現金支付保釋金就行了
and you pay a straight cash bail.
跟阿爾布開克完全不一樣
It's not like Albuquerque at all.
瑪麗恩  你還在聽嗎
Marion, you still there?
嗯  為什么...
Yeah. Why--
為什么杰夫聯系的是你  而不是我
Why did Jeff call you instead of me?
他可能怕你一下接受不過來吧
Well, I think he was scared at how you'd take it.
說真的  我都打算直接付保釋金了
Honestly, I was gonna pay the bail myself,
但后來想想  還是應該由親屬來辦
but I think it should be a family member.
這樣最好
I think that'd be best.
這樣吧  我去洗個澡  換好衣服
I'll tell you what, I'm gonna take a shower, get dressed.
你也這么做
And you do the same.
我待會過去接你
I'll swing by and pick you up.
然后我們去把事情解決
We'll get this whole thing squared away.
巴迪呢  他有麻煩嗎
Wh-what about Buddy? Is he in any trouble?
沒有吧
I don't think so.
他為什么會有麻煩
Why would he be?
我們大概一小時后見
I'll see you in about an hour.
好的  好的  謝謝
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Thanks.
*不*
*Oh, no, oh*
*大潮...*
*The tide i--*
*傷我至深的*
*That tease and hurt me bad*
*是你對待我的方式*
*But it's the way you do the things you do to me*
*我不是那種*
*I'm not the kinda girl*
*輕言放棄的女孩*
*Who gives up just like that*
*不*
*Oh, no, oh*
*大潮洶涌*
*The tide is high*
*但我仍在堅持*
*But I'm holding on*
*我會成為你的第...*
*I'm gonna be your num--*
*我不是那種輕言放棄的女孩*
*I'm not the kinda girl who gives up*
瑪麗恩
Marion!
*輕言放棄的女孩*
*Just like that*
*不*
*Oh, no*
瑪麗恩
Marion!
Marion?
瑪麗恩
你還好吧
Everything okay?
很好  抱歉
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry.
我只是忘了時間
I-- I just lost track of the time.
沒關系
That's okay.
你要不要去換件衣服
Uh, you wanna put some clothes on
我們好出發
so that we can get moving?
怎么樣
What do you say?
那個  我...
Uh, you know, well, I, I...
我不想耽誤事
I don't wanna slow things down.
要不還是你自己去吧
I think maybe you oughta go without me.
...派對狂歡  想著自己的事
...partying, minding my own business.
你被捕了
You are under arrest.
我最好打給索爾
I better call Saul!
我是索爾·古德曼
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman.
你知道你有權利嗎
Did you know that you have rights?
憲法說你有  我也說你有
The Constitution says you do, and so do I.
我相信  在被證明有罪之前
I believe that, until proven guilty,
這個國家所有的男人  女人  小孩都是無辜的
every man, woman, and child in this country is innocent.
所以我會為你而戰  阿爾布開克
And that's why I fight for you, Albuquerque!
這是什么
What's that?
你說呢
You tell me.
瑪麗恩  你覺得這是我嗎
Marion, do you think that's me?
這不是我
'Cause it's not.
從來就沒有咬咬  對嗎
There never was a Nippy, was there?
杰夫跟你說什么了
What did Jeff tell you?
他什么也沒說
Oh, he didn't tell me anything.
是搜索引擎告訴我的
Ask Jeeves told me.
我輸入了"騙子"和"阿爾布開克"
I typed in "Con man" and "Albuquerque,"
你的大名就跳出來了  明晃晃的
and up you popped, big as day.
你干什么  瑪麗恩
What are you doing, Marion?
你說呢  我要報警
What do you think I'm doing? I'm calling the police.
來  我來幫你
Here, lemme help you with that.
聽著  我想我們應該
Listen, I think we're losing sight
著眼于大局  對不對
of the bigger picture here, okay?
杰夫現在有麻煩  而我想幫他
Jeff is in trouble, and I wanna help him.
我和他都需要你的支持
He and I sure could use your support here.
你把我兒子卷進什么事里了
What did you get my son into?
都是他自愿做的一些事
Nothing that he didn't ask for.
聽著
Now, listen,
我還是你認識的那個好朋友
I'm still the good friend you thought I was, okay?
杰夫理解我  巴迪理解我
Jeff understands me, Buddy understands me.
你也會理解我的
And you will, too.
只是  你得
It's just, you have to, uh,
不要節外生枝  好嗎
you know, keep things on an even keel, all right?
你手里拿的什么
What have you got there?
把它放下
Put that down.
放下  瑪麗恩
Put that down, Marion.
放下
Put it down.
別這么做  瑪麗恩
Do not do it, Marion.
最后一次警告
Final warning.
我信任過你
I trusted you.
瑪麗恩  我是生命警報的瓦萊麗
Marion? This is Valerie with Life Alert.
你還好嗎
Are you okay?
不  瓦萊麗  我不好
No, Valerie, I'm not okay.
有個罪犯正站在我的廚房里  威脅我
There's a criminal standing in my kitchen, threatening me!
他是一個通緝犯
He's a wanted man,
名叫索爾·古德曼
and his name is Saul Goodman!
好的  瑪麗恩  我來報警
All right, Marion, I'm calling the police.
我現在就撥電話
I'm calling right now.